dclottery.com 2008-12-17

# DC Lottery - Privacy Policy

##  WEBSITE PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY

The District of Columbia Lottery and Charitable Games Control Board ("D.C. Lottery") is committed to protecting the rights of all our visitors. We recognize our obligation to keep sensitive information secure and have created this privacy statement to share our information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

###  Collection and Use of Online Information

Our web server automatically collects your IP address when you visit our site. (Your IP address is your computer's unique address that lets other computers attached to the Internet know where to send data, but does not identify you individually.) We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to compile statistics on site usage. We do not make your IP address available to anyone outside the D.C. Lottery.

To provide better service and a more effective website, sections of this site may use "cookies" as part of our interaction with your browser. A cookie is a small text file (typically only a few bytes) that we place on your hard drive to allow our server to identify your computer. Our cookies will not attempt to read any information on your hard drive, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to determine your identity or your email address. 

When you visit certain areas of this site, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) that we need to process your request. In the event that you decline to provide such information, you limit our ability to serve you. Still, we invite you to continue to visit the site and take advantage of the wealth of information it offers. 

The D.C. Lottery may occasionally survey website users for their voluntary opinions on games or other matters of interest to lottery players, as well as for marketing and/or statistical analysis. 

###  Secure Transmissions

Please be assured that this site has security measures in place to protect the information you provide us. We encrypt information that is deemed sensitive or data that must remain secure to meet legal requirements.

###  Protection of Personal Information

Your personal information is available only to D.C. Lottery employees who have a need to know it. It will not be available for public inspection without your consent. However, we may collect or disclose personal information if the collection or disclosure is: (1) necessary to perform the legal duties of the D.C. Lottery; (2) authorized by the District of Columbia Freedom of Information Act or other District of Columbia or federal statute or regulation; (3) made pursuant to a subpoena, court order or by law, (4) for the purposes of validating the identity of the user, or (5) used solely for statistical purposes in a form that can not be used to identify any particular person. Also, no site user information will be shared, sold, or transferred to any third party without your prior consent. Access is given only to those qualified professionals who provide D.C. Lottery services consistent with your interactions with our site. 

###  Right to Inspect, Amend, or Correct Personal Records

Every site user who provides us with personal information has the right to inspect, amend, or correct his or her own personal information. You may ask to inspect your personal information by sending an [email to us](mailto:contactus@dclottery.com). 

###  Other Sites

D.C. Lottery's privacy policy extends to D.C. Lottery's websites only. If you link to another entity's website through the www.dclottery.com website, you should read that entity's privacy and security policy to determine its website practices. 

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please [ contact us](mailto:contactus@dclottery.com).
